padtube.com 2016-02-22

# Privacy Policy - padtube.com

This Privacy Policy describes padtube.com policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. padtube.com receives your information through our various web sites, APIs, applications, services and third-parties ("Services"). For example, you send us information when you use padtube.com from our web site, post ads, receive ads or access our site any resources. When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by padtube.com in the Turkey or any other country where padtube.com operates.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [](mailto:privacy@padtube.com)[privacy@padtube.com](mailto:privacy@padtube.com).

##### Collection and Use of Information

Information Collected Upon Registration. When you create or reconfigure a padtube.com account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, username, password, and email address. Some of this information, for example, your name and username, is listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page and in search results. Some Services, such as classified ads, optimized web search and viewing lists, do not require registration.

Additional Information. You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as a short product description, your location, or picture. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or the instructions on our web site. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. Providing the additional information described in this section is entirely optional.

Classfied Ads, Site Listing, Business Listing and other Public Information. Our Services are primarily focused to help you expose information of your product here in the Philippines(for now). Most of the information you provide to us is information you are asking us to make public except your conversation with your potential buyer. You should be careful about all information that will be made public by padtube.com, not just your Ads.

Data Logs. Our servers automatically record information ("Data Logs") created by your use of the Services. Data Logs may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with our website, applications and advertisements, may also be included in Data Logs. If we have not already deleted the Data Logs earlier, we will either delete it after 2 years.

Links. padtube.com may keep track of how you interact with links in Optimized Web Search across our Services including third party services and clients by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, including advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.

Cookies. Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as searching and looking at classified lists. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. padtube.com may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

Third Party Services. padtube.com uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our Services, such as hosting our various blogs and wikis, and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request.

##### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Your Consent. We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client or application to access your padtube.com account.

Service Providers. We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy.

Law and Harm. We may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect padtube.com rights or property.

Business Transfers. In the event that padtube.com is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

##### Modifying Your Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account. Our Policy Towards Children Our Services are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [privacy@padtube.com](mailto:privacy@padtube.com). We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

##### Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at http://padtube.com/privacy-25. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via an e-mail associated with your account.

By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
